<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on webtor.io</title>
    <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on webtor.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Redesign and other cool features</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/redesign-and-other-cool-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/redesign-and-other-cool-features/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The web interface got a fresh redesign! We&amp;rsquo;ve reworked many components to make everything look and feel more polished — cleaner layout, more pleasant visuals, better responsiveness on mobile devices. But the redesign isn&amp;rsquo;t just about looks, it also brought a bunch of important improvements under the hood:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toast notifications&lt;/strong&gt; - now when you perform actions like copying a link, adding to library, or deleting an item, you&amp;rsquo;ll see a neat notification popup confirming the action. Earlier, there was no visual feedback for many of these actions and you had to guess whether your click actually did something. Now you get clear success, error, or info messages that appear briefly and disappear on their own.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Status icons in progress log&lt;/strong&gt; - the progress log that shows during file processing now uses clear visual icons: a checkmark for completed steps, a cross for errors, and a warning sign for warnings. Earlier, the status was shown as text labels like &lt;code&gt;[done]&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;[error]&lt;/code&gt;, which was harder to read, especially on mobile.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smoother video playback start&lt;/strong&gt; - earlier, when you started watching a video, the player could stutter or buffer during the first moments while the transcoder was warming up. Now the system pre-buffers up to 5 minutes of HLS video segments right after the transcoder starts, ensuring smooth playback from the very first second.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automatic restart of failed jobs&lt;/strong&gt; - earlier, if a background job (like transcoding or downloading) failed with an error, it would stay in that error state and you had to trigger it again manually. Now errored jobs automatically restart when re-requested, so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about stale failures.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/&#34;&gt;webtor.io&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;sponsor it&lt;/a&gt; if you wish!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seedbox vs torrent vault: what&#39;s the difference?</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/seedbox-vs-torrent-vault/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:20:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/seedbox-vs-torrent-vault/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When torrents become part of a regular workflow, traditional torrent clients often stop being enough.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users begin looking for more stable ways to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;keep torrents available&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;access content reliably&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;avoid depending on their local devices&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Two approaches appear frequently in this context: &lt;strong&gt;seedboxes&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;torrent vaults&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While they may seem similar at first glance, they solve different problems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-a-seedbox-is&#34;&gt;What a seedbox is&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A seedbox is a remote server designed for torrent downloading and seeding.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a personal torrent library</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/personal-torrent-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:18:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/personal-torrent-library/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For many people, torrents are a temporary tool.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You download a file, use it once, and move on.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;But over time, some users begin to treat torrents differently — not as one-time transfers, but as part of a personal collection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A personal torrent library is not just about saving files.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s about keeping access to content that matters to you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-people-start-building-torrent-libraries&#34;&gt;Why people start building torrent libraries&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The shift usually happens after a few familiar experiences:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to keep rare torrents available</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/keep-rare-torrents-available/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:16:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/keep-rare-torrents-available/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rare torrents disappear faster than most people expect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A file that works today may be impossible to download a few weeks later.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Once seeders leave, the torrent becomes fragile — and sometimes vanishes completely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you care about keeping specific torrents accessible, relying on chance is rarely enough.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Availability needs to be intentional.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-rare-torrents-need-special-attention&#34;&gt;Why rare torrents need special attention&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Popular torrents survive because many people download and seed them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rare torrents don&amp;rsquo;t have that advantage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why torrents disappear over time</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/why-torrents-disappear/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:13:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/why-torrents-disappear/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At first glance, torrents feel permanent.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once a torrent exists, it seems like it should always be available. The metadata is shared, trackers can be copied, and magnet links don&amp;rsquo;t depend on a single server.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But in reality, torrents disappear all the time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not because the technology fails — but because the ecosystem around them changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;torrents-dont-live-on-servers&#34;&gt;Torrents don&amp;rsquo;t live on servers&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unlike traditional downloads, torrents are not stored in one place.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Torrent has no seeds — what can you do?</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/torrent-no-seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:10:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/torrent-no-seeds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Few things are more frustrating than finding the exact torrent you need — only to discover it has no seeds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The file exists, the metadata is there, but nothing downloads.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;No progress, no peers, no activity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This situation is common, and it&amp;rsquo;s not a temporary glitch. It&amp;rsquo;s a natural part of how torrents work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To understand what you can do, it helps to understand why torrents disappear in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vault is live — keep torrents available even without seeders</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/vault-is-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:50:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/vault-is-live/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve just launched one of Webtor’s core features — Vault.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vault lets you keep torrents available even when there are no seeders.&#xA;If a torrent matters to you, you can now make sure it stays online and accessible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;⸻&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;🧱 &lt;strong&gt;How Vault works&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each membership tier now includes Vault Points (VP):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1 Vault Point = 1 GB&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You can invest Vault Points into a torrent&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;As long as your points are invested, the torrent stays available in Vault&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When your subscription is active, your funded torrents remain accessible&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vault is especially useful for:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you really need a VPN for torrents?</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/vpn-for-torrents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 21:47:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/vpn-for-torrents/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For many people, torrents and VPNs are almost inseparable.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever searched for anything related to torrenting, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably seen the same advice repeated over and over: &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Always use a VPN.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But is that actually true in every case?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And more importantly — &lt;strong&gt;what exactly changes depending on how you download or stream torrents?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s break it down without myths or marketing promises.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-people-use-vpns-with-torrents&#34;&gt;Why people use VPNs with torrents&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main reason VPNs are commonly recommended for torrents comes from how &lt;strong&gt;traditional torrent clients&lt;/strong&gt; work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Torrent streaming vs downloading: what&#39;s the difference?</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/torrent-streaming-vs-downloading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 21:47:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/torrent-streaming-vs-downloading/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Torrents have traditionally been associated with downloading files and waiting until the process is complete.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;But over time, another approach has become more common: &lt;strong&gt;torrent streaming&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Both methods work with the same torrent data, yet the experience is very different.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Understanding this difference helps you choose the right option for your situation instead of defaulting to old habits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-classic-torrent-downloading-works&#34;&gt;How classic torrent downloading works&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With traditional torrent downloading, the goal is simple:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;get the entire file onto your device&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Torrent vs magnet link: what&#39;s the real difference?</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/torrent-vs-magnet-link/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 21:47:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/torrent-vs-magnet-link/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Torrent files and magnet links are often treated as interchangeable.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;In practice, many users don&amp;rsquo;t even think about the difference — they just click whatever is available.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, these two formats are not the same, and understanding how they differ helps explain why some workflows feel faster, simpler, or more reliable than others.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s look at what actually separates a torrent file from a magnet link.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-a-torrent-file-is&#34;&gt;What a torrent file is&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A torrent file is a small metadata file that describes the content you want to download.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why torrent clients don&#39;t work well on iPhone</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/torrent-clients-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 21:47:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/torrent-clients-iphone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever tried to use torrents on an iPhone, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably noticed that the experience is frustrating — or simply impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unlike desktop systems, iOS was never designed with peer-to-peer file sharing in mind.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This isn&amp;rsquo;t an accident, and it&amp;rsquo;s not something that can be easily fixed with &amp;ldquo;better apps&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s look at why torrent clients struggle on iPhone and what actually causes these limitations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;ios-was-built-around-strict-app-isolation&#34;&gt;iOS was built around strict app isolation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the core design principles of iOS is &lt;strong&gt;sandboxing&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why torrents are often blocked on public Wi-Fi</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/torrents-blocked-public-wifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 21:47:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/torrents-blocked-public-wifi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever tried to use torrents on public Wi-Fi — at a café, hotel, airport, or university — you may have noticed a familiar pattern:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;websites work fine, streaming works fine, but torrent clients either don&amp;rsquo;t connect at all or crawl at unusable speeds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This isn&amp;rsquo;t a coincidence, and it&amp;rsquo;s not a temporary glitch.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Public networks are often designed to restrict torrent traffic by default.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s look at why this happens.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas &amp; Happy New Year — thank you for this year</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/merry-christmas-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/merry-christmas-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey friends,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Merry Christmas 🎄 and Happy New Year!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before the year ends, I want to sincerely thank everyone who supports Webtor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year we didn’t just add features — we turned Webtor into a more complete and useful tool.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What we built together this year:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Libraries&lt;/strong&gt; — your personal space for saved content&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WebDAV&lt;/strong&gt; — mount Webtor as a drive and work with files directly&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stremio integration&lt;/strong&gt; — including full support for Stremio addons&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Debrid service integration&lt;/strong&gt; — Real-Debrid, TorBox, and others&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your support doesn’t just pay for servers — it buys time, focus, and the freedom to build things properly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday Sale — 37% Off on All Plans</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/black-friday-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/black-friday-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey folks!&#xA;Black Friday is here — and I’m rolling out the biggest discount of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Get 37% off on all Webtor plans until December 1.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;👉 &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/donate&#34;&gt;https://webtor.io/donate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your support keeps the project growing, faster, and more fun to build. And with Vault on the way, this winter is going to be big.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks for being part of this journey — enjoy the deal while it lasts! 🚀&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Debrid and Torbox as Streaming Backends</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/real-debrid-and-torbox-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/real-debrid-and-torbox-integration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You can now connect Real-Debrid and Torbox accounts in Webtor as custom streaming backends.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They’ll act as additional caches for Stremio — giving you faster playback and more available streams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;-how-it-works&#34;&gt;🧩 How it works&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Go to Webtor Profile&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Scroll to the &lt;strong&gt;Streaming Backends&lt;/strong&gt; section&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add your API key from Real-Debrid or Torbox&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set the priority order — which backend should be used first (don&amp;rsquo;t forget to click &amp;ldquo;Save&amp;rdquo; button)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the content isn’t found in any Debrid cache, Webtor’s own streaming engine will be used as a fallback, so playback always works.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webtor &#43; Torrentio = ⚡</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/webtor-torrentio-stremio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/webtor-torrentio-stremio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Big milestone! 🎉&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve just made Webtor and Torrentio (and other Stremio addons) work together  🚀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now Webtor can stream not only your library, but also any content coming from Stremio addons.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how it works under the hood:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Webtor queries all your connected Stremio addons (up to 3)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Duplicates are removed (deduplication)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Results are filtered by your preferred quality (720p / 1080p / 4K)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Every stream is enriched with a direct Webtor streaming link&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So now you can stream not only your personal library, but also any content from Stremio addons — instantly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebDAV is here!</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/webdav-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/webdav-is-here/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks to your support, another big feature just landed — WebDAV access to your Webtor library.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can now mount your whole torrent collection as a network folder on desktop or mobile. Stream directly from your library — or just copy your stuff locally.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And yes — you can upload new torrents too — just drop .torrent files into the &lt;code&gt;torrents/&lt;/code&gt; folder. That’s it. 🤘&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;🧩 Works great with:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mountain Duck (macOS/Windows)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;RaiDrive (Windows)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Owlfiles (iOS / Android) — tested and working without hassle&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;rclone — for CLI and selfhosted automation fans&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;💬 If you tried any other client — and it worked or didn’t — feel free to message me or comment here. The more we know, the better the experience for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Updates</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/summer-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/summer-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone 👋&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just wanted to share some small but important updates that have just landed on Webtor — all thanks to your support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;✅ What’s new:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;🔐 &lt;strong&gt;Google login&lt;/strong&gt; — I noticed that around 70% of users log in with Google email anyway, so I decided to make things more straightforward by adding a simple Google login option.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;🎁 &lt;strong&gt;Patreon login&lt;/strong&gt; — There were a lot of issues where users struggled to get their benefits from paid subscriptions (especially those who used Apple login on Patreon). Now every backer can simply log in with their Patreon account — no more issues.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help Us Grow — 🎁 Get Premium Access as a Thank You</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/community-sharing-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/community-sharing-program/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Love Webtor? Want to support the project without spending money?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now you can — by helping others discover it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re launching a simple community sharing program:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;mention Webtor in relevant places — and get free premium access as a thank-you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;✨ How It Works&#xA;Just share Webtor where it makes sense — on Reddit, in Telegram or Discord groups, on your blog or social media — anywhere people discuss torrents and streaming.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch your torrents on TV – with Stremio!</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-your-torrents-on-tv-with-stremio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-your-torrents-on-tv-with-stremio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve been slowly moving toward this — and now it’s finally here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The personal library feature was just a stop on the way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The real goal was always this: streaming your own torrents directly on your TV, with no downloads, no VPN, and no torrent client. Just press play.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And now it works. It’s been live for a full day in production — and I’m absolutely happy with how it performs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Library just got a major upgrade!</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/library-major-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/library-major-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey friends! 👋&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve just released a huge improvement to Webtor Library — and we think you’re going to love it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, when you open your Library, you’ll see new sections for Movies and Series — automatically created based on the torrents you’ve added.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s a cleaner, smarter way to browse your saved content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No more endless torrent lists — just organized, beautiful media.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What’s next?&#xA;Soon you’ll be able to:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New in Webtor: Personal Library &#43; Big Plans Ahead!</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/personal-library-and-big-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/personal-library-and-big-plans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey friends! 👋&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today I’m excited to share a new feature we’ve just launched in Webtor:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personal Library&lt;/strong&gt; — now you can easily save torrents you like into your personal space! Just click “Add to Library” under any loaded torrent. 🎯&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Save favorite torrents&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sort your library by newest or by name&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But that’s not all!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Coming soon:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automatic movie metadata fetching&lt;/strong&gt; — Webtor will recognize movies in your library and fetch posters, titles, descriptions, and more!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integration with Stremio&lt;/strong&gt; — stream your library content directly through Stremio!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for your support — you’re making this possible. 🙏&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year from Webtor.io! 🎉</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/happy-new-year-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 12:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/happy-new-year-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To celebrate the spirit of New Year, we’re excited to offer 100 lucky people an exclusive gift: 1 month of free access to Webtor.io!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What does this mean for you?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;• Unlimited access to seamless torrent streaming.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;• Enjoy your favorite content instantly without downloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;🚀 How to claim your gift?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s simple! Be one of the first 100 to sign up using this exclusive link: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/pavel_tatarskiy/redeem/E323E&#34;&gt;https://www.patreon.com/pavel_tatarskiy/redeem/E323E&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you already have paid tier, you can always share your link with your friends!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Transcoding System!</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-transcoding-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 18:32:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-transcoding-system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We’ve revamped the transcoding system and introduced some exciting new features:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;faster-transcoding-startup&#34;&gt;Faster Transcoding Startup&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Previously, transcoding was initiated in a separate container, which took additional time to launch. Now, transcoding starts immediately without delays.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;efficient-caching&#34;&gt;Efficient Caching&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Transcoding results are now cached more effectively. Content is only removed when it’s no longer in use, rather than based on a fixed time limit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, the improved transcoding system has reduced our reliance on Kubernetes cluster components. This paves the way for us to release a single Docker image version of webtor.io early next year!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet web-ui version 2!</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/meet-web-ui-version-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 15:07:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/meet-web-ui-version-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Meet web-ui version 2!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The back was completely rewritten from Node.js to Golang, and the front became as lightweight as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s new?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dark and light themes&lt;/strong&gt; - now you can change the interface settings depending on your&#xA;preferences (the system color scheme will be used by default).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Authorization&lt;/strong&gt; - authorization used to be only through Patreon, now you can log in&#xA;simply using your email address.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clear progress&lt;/strong&gt; - now you can see how the process of preparing the torrent for playback is going on&#xA;and the jump and at what specific stage the problem arose.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved download speed&lt;/strong&gt; - the volume of downloaded scripts and styles has been reduced by 5 times!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/&#34;&gt;webtor.io&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;sponsor it&lt;/a&gt; if you wish!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.16.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.16.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 21:34:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.16.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last release of the year!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The outgoing year was extremely difficult for the project. In addition to development, it was necessary&#xA;resolve issues related to finding a new hosting and payment methods. But luckily, it&amp;rsquo;s over now! 😆😆😆&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, the list of changes (as usual):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shorter time to download&lt;/strong&gt; - earlier, before the start of the download, a new torrent client was launched, which could&#xA;take 5-10 seconds, and only after that the search for peers and the actual download itself began. Now, a certain number of&#xA;torrent clients are working in the cluster all the time, which can process several torrent downloads simultaneously, this&#xA;made it possible to remove just those 5-10 seconds necessary for a cold start.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Long-lasting cache&lt;/strong&gt; - earlier, if no one accessed the torrent client, then after 10 minutes it turned off and all&#xA;downloaded data disappeared with it. Now data is deleted only if there is no room left on the server and only the oldest&#xA;unused files are deleted. This allows to save the downloaded information for a longer period.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Work has begun on the next version of the web interface, more details can be found on&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/webtor-io/web-ui-v2&#34;&gt;its repository page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webtor API v1.0.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/webtor-api-v1.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 19:17:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/webtor-api-v1.0.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I present to your attention the Webtor API! &amp;#x1f389;&amp;#x1f389;&amp;#x1f389;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Webtor API allows you to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Download torrent content without usage of BitTorrent-client.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Stream content instantly with on-the-fly transcoding. Webtor generates HLS-streams suitable for web-streaming.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fetch &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.opensubtitles.org/&#34;&gt;OpenSubtitles.org&lt;/a&gt; for torrent content.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Great and how to access it? There are two options to choose from here:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Host it on your hardware as part of a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/webtor-io/helm-charts&#34;&gt;self-hosted solution&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Connect via &lt;a href=&#34;https://rapidapi.com/paveltatarsky-Dx4aX7s_XBt/api/webtor/&#34;&gt;RapidAPI&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/&#34;&gt;webtor.io&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;sponsor it&lt;/a&gt; if you wish!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.15.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.15.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 19:23:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.15.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt; has finally moved completely to Open Source, what does this mean:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All code for all project components is now &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/webtor-io&#34;&gt;publicly available on Github&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Now it is possible to deploy &lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt; at home. &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/webtor-io/helm-charts&#34;&gt;Installation script attached&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Future plans:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add REST-API, this should make it easier to programmatically use the service.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Implement support for external HTTP links as a source.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/&#34;&gt;webtor.io&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;sponsor it&lt;/a&gt; if you wish!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.14.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.14.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 22:48:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.14.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Latest release of this year!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before announcing the list of changes, I want to share with you great news!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In anticipation of the upcoming holidays, the speed has been increased for all who support the project!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bronze Backer 15Mbit/s =&amp;gt; 20Mbit/s&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Silver Backer 25Mbit/s =&amp;gt; 50Mbit/s&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Gold Backer   50Mbit/s =&amp;gt; 100Mbit/s&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And here is the list of changes itself:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support for Zip64&lt;/strong&gt; - now there is no limit on the size of files placed in a ZIP archive, previously there was a limit of 4GB.&#xA;(I&amp;rsquo;m also thinking about supporting the TAR format, write if someone else is also interested in this!)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resumed support for Google Chromecast&lt;/strong&gt; - now you can immediately stream your content to any device with support of&#xA;Google Chromecast. During playback, the corresponding icon appears in the upper right corner of the player.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to your support, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/webtor-io/&#34;&gt;part of the project moved to Open Source&lt;/a&gt;, which allowed great projects to appear:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.13.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.13.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 16:38:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.13.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of the key changes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;️Resume download bug fixed&lt;/strong&gt; - now, in the case of a failure during downloading, resuming works correctly,&#xA;this applies to downloads of both individual files and downloads in a ZIP archive.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fewer drops and crashes&lt;/strong&gt; - earlier, during component releases, all downloads were interrupted, now they just pause&#xA;at the time of the update.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Torrent files live forever&lt;/strong&gt; - previously torrent files were deleted after a certain time, now they are saved forever, this&#xA;allows less frequent access to the BitTorrent network and improves response time. (this does not apply to downloadable content!)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.12.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.12.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:05:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.12.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of the key changes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;️Progressive enhancement for video formats&lt;/strong&gt; - previously popular video-content was only cached to avoid the need of periodic&#xA;trnasmitting from the BitTorrent-network. Now the video is deferredly converted to various formats for optimal mobile playback&#xA;(adaptive bitrate streaming).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved loading of cached HLS-fragments&lt;/strong&gt; - now cached fragments are loaded with lookahead, thus on request&#xA;the necessary fragment has already been preloaded to the edge-server from the main cache-storage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/&#34;&gt;webtor.io&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;sponsor it&lt;/a&gt; if you wish!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.11.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.11.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:05:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.11.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of the key changes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;️Download has become clearer and more convenient&lt;/strong&gt; - now, when downloading, a separate form opens with the progress of the download, and the ability to copy the download link. It is also possible to generate a bash command to download via &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gnu.org/software/wget/&#34;&gt;Wget&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Player SDK has now been renamed to Embed SDK&lt;/strong&gt; - at some point it became clear that &lt;strong&gt;webtor&lt;/strong&gt; could be integrated not only in the form of a player and the &amp;ldquo;Player SDK&amp;rdquo; name would be misleading.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can now download the torrent as an archive on your website&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/webtor-io/embed-sdk-js&#34;&gt;Embed SDK&lt;/a&gt; can now, in addition to the player, integrate a download form similar to download form at &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io&#34;&gt;webtor.io&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved MP4 streaming at 1080p&lt;/strong&gt; - improved MP4 playback at 1080p, reduced latency during playback (on desktop).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fixed transcoding content errors&lt;/strong&gt; - there was an error with a delay in the start of playback.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/&#34;&gt;webtor.io&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;sponsor it&lt;/a&gt; if you wish!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.10.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.10.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 21:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.10.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of the key changes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Badge with heart ❤️&lt;/strong&gt; - now every backer can see their status in the top menu.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Easier to share links&lt;/strong&gt; - now you can generate direct links like &lt;code&gt;https://webtor.io/%infohash%&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;https://webtor.io/%magnet-uri%&lt;/code&gt;.&#xA;The ability to generate them from the interface has also been added, just click &amp;ldquo;Share link&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Player embed code generation&lt;/strong&gt; - now the &amp;ldquo;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;/&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&amp;rdquo;, appears in the video player, which allows you to generate&#xA;a code for inserting the player on your website or blog.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Displaying the transcoding process&lt;/strong&gt; - now the player shows the progress of transcoding, and the time rail hightlights already transcoded fragment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;External subtitles are also available for mobile devices&lt;/strong&gt; - previously, when selecting OpenSubtitles  they did not play on mobile devices,&#xA;but now it is working.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transcoding errors are visible&lt;/strong&gt; - now if a transcoding error occurs, its cause is immediately displayed in the player window.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/webtor-io/player-sdk-js&#34;&gt;player SDK&lt;/a&gt; an alternative method for initializing the player was added,&#xA;now you can simply embed the script and specify the Magnet-URI in the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;video&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tag:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.9.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.9.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 21:17:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.9.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First release of this year!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of the key changes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expanded list of supported formats&lt;/strong&gt; - added support for video files with .ts and .vob extensions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instant switching between audio tracks&lt;/strong&gt; - previously, when an alternative audio track was selected,&#xA;playback started from the very beginning. Now all tracks are converted at the same time, allowing you&#xA;to switch between them on the fly. The selection of audio tracks has been moved to the subtitles menu.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content caching has been improved&lt;/strong&gt; - during playback, the following fragments are loaded in the background,&#xA;which makes smoother playback. Also, transcoded fragments began to be cached.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minor interface improvements&lt;/strong&gt; - added an indication of the file size in the listing, rounded corners of elements.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/&#34;&gt;webtor.io&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;sponsor it&lt;/a&gt; if you wish!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.8.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.8.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:20:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.8.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Latest release of this year!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of the key changes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The main page has been improved&lt;/strong&gt; - now there is a field for entering a magnet-link (by the way, now you can use just infohash).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resuming the download of the ZIP-archive after break&lt;/strong&gt; - now when downloading the ZIP-archive, the browser will display the full size of the downloaded archive, and you can also pause and resume downloading the archive from the same location.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;View video only via HLS&lt;/strong&gt; - now mp4 format is also converted to HLS on-the-fly. Thanks to this, it was possible&#xA;implement the ability to save bandwidth by sharing HLS-fragments via &lt;a href=&#34;https://webrtc.org/&#34;&gt;WebRTC&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Novage/p2p-media-loader&#34;&gt;p2p-media-loader&lt;/a&gt; library&#xA;(&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/webtorrent/webtorrent&#34;&gt;WebTorrent&lt;/a&gt; had to be abandoned due to large delays at the beginning of playback).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Added a lot of features to the player SDK&lt;/strong&gt; - now in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/webtor-io/player-sdk-js&#34;&gt;SDK&lt;/a&gt; you can specify&#xA;which elements of the player should be disabled. It became possible to stretch the player simultaneously in width and height by 100%.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Switching between files in the player&lt;/strong&gt; - now you can switch between files within folder without leaving the player&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/&#34;&gt;webtor.io&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;sponsor it&lt;/a&gt; if you wish!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous and Secure</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/anonymous-and-secure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 20:52:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/anonymous-and-secure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quite often I get asked questions about how secure it is to use &lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt; and how does using &lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;differ from using a regular &lt;strong&gt;BitTorrent&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It also turned out that in some countries the use of &lt;strong&gt;BitTorrent&lt;/strong&gt;-networks for downloading this or that content&#xA;can be potentially dangerous and lead to substantial fines (eg in Germany).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To understand this issue, let&amp;rsquo;s understand the principles of the &lt;strong&gt;webtor.io&lt;/strong&gt; service.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When visiting the &lt;strong&gt;webtor.io&lt;/strong&gt; website, the user always opens a secure &lt;strong&gt;SSL&lt;/strong&gt;-connection and&#xA;all further requests between the client and the server are transmitted encrypted using the &lt;strong&gt;HTTPS&lt;/strong&gt;-protocol.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;At the time of downloading content, only webtor servers connects to &lt;strong&gt;BitTorrent&lt;/strong&gt;-peers.&#xA;For the end-user, downloading a file from &lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt; is no different than downloading from any&#xA;other file hosting service, and watching a video is similar to watching a video from a &lt;strong&gt;Tube&lt;/strong&gt;-site.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt; servers work like regular &lt;strong&gt;BitTorrent&lt;/strong&gt;-clients. Thus, through &lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt; you can load&#xA;any torrents that could be downloaded through a regular &lt;strong&gt;BitTorrent&lt;/strong&gt;-client (including torrent files from private trackers),&#xA;but without revealing the real &lt;strong&gt;IP&lt;/strong&gt;-addresses for the rest of the &lt;strong&gt;BitTorrent&lt;/strong&gt;-network users&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thus, it is not necessary to use &lt;strong&gt;VPN&lt;/strong&gt;-services when visiting &lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt; and&#xA;downloading torrents via &lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt; is anonymous and secure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webtor.io vs WebTorrent vs μTorrent Web</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/webtor.io-vs-webtorrent-vs-%CE%BCtorrent-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 18:09:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/webtor.io-vs-webtorrent-vs-%CE%BCtorrent-web/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello! This time I decided to write some comparison of my service and other similar ones. Perhaps many&#xA;moments will seem a little biased to you, but alas, I have been developing this service for a long time and I can be a little subject.&#xA;I can also write a little bit more detailed about my service because I know it a little better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The BitTorrent protocol has been around since 2001 and is used to transfer files, videos and music to this day,&#xA;despite various restrictions in a number of countries. During this time, a large number of BitTorrent clients appeared,&#xA;implementing this protocol, with the ability to download and streaming.&#xA;If earlier the BitTorrent client was associated only with Desktop applications, now many of them&#xA;stepped towards web applications and suddenly opened in a web browser. Let&amp;rsquo;s try to figure it out&#xA;in this variety of Web-Torrent clients. For comparison were selected:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.7.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.7.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 22:59:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.7.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It has been quite a while since the previous release, but it was worth it!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of key changes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Player SDK is already available!&lt;/strong&gt; - Now you can embed the playback of torrent content in any site without extra effort. SDK with an example&#xA;usage &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/webtor-io/player-sdk-js&#34;&gt;published to Github&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interface for selecting and displaying subtitles improved&lt;/strong&gt; - it became much easier to select subtitles from a large list, as well as the opportunity&#xA;to change subtitle size on the fly.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dark mode by default&lt;/strong&gt; - now the main color scheme of the interface is solved in dark shades by default. They say it protects our eyes!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Caching of downloaded content improved&lt;/strong&gt; - now all downloaded content is saved for a day and does not require re-downloading from the BitTorrent network.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WebRTC support&lt;/strong&gt; - if several users watch the same movie, then they exchange fragments of it by the &lt;a href=&#34;https://webrtc.org/&#34;&gt;WebRTC&lt;/a&gt; protocol.&#xA;This uses a private tracker. Only MP4 is currently supported.&#xA;This was made possible thanks to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/webtorrent/webtorrent&#34;&gt;WebTorrent&lt;/a&gt; project.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now all server components of the Webtor platform and SDK are available opensource:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.6.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 16:52:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.6.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This release was mainly focused on stability and fixing performance issues of the service.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most affected component was transcoding. Here is a short list of changes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dropped HEVC-support&lt;/strong&gt; - transcoding from HEVC(x265) to h264(x264) is a really heavy lifting that freezes work of whole service.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dropped &amp;ldquo;fast forward&amp;rdquo; functionality&lt;/strong&gt; - now transcoding starts always from the beginning. It makes possible to just repack stream&#xA;to HLS instead of &amp;ldquo;real transcoding&amp;rdquo;. This change also dramatically insreases quality of h264-based video. Also &amp;ldquo;fast forward&amp;rdquo; freezes&#xA;sometimes and looks quite unreliable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here we see an example of reducing features in favor of image quality and service stability.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.5.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.5.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 01:01:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.5.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of new November&amp;rsquo;s features:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenSubtitles suppport&lt;/strong&gt; - now &lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt; automatically loads all available subtitles from OpenSubtitles.org for your preffered language.&#xA;All subtitles are available under player&amp;rsquo;s &lt;strong&gt;CC&lt;/strong&gt; button.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/&#34;&gt;webtor.io&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;sponsor it&lt;/a&gt; if you wish!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technologies inside Webtor.io</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/technologies-inside-webtor.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 21:47:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/technologies-inside-webtor.io/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/images/technologies-inside-webtor/kittens.jpg&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;Periodically, my users are interested in what technologies &lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt; is based on,&#xA;whether I use library A or tool B. This time I want to fully answer all questions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To begin with, &lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt; has made a 3-year-long journey from a monolithic application living on a dedicated server&#xA;to the introduction of microservices, containerization, and moving to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes (k8s)&lt;/a&gt; cluster.&#xA;Currently, about 10 different services are running in the cluster and 100+ simultaneous jobs are running&#xA;for downloading torrents and transcoding content.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.4.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 21:28:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.4.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of new October&amp;rsquo;s features:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download ZIP-archive&lt;/strong&gt; - now you can push &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Download as ZIP-archive&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; button and downloading of the current folder will start immediately.&#xA;But there might be some delay in case if there is no available peers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Share&amp;rdquo; button&lt;/strong&gt; - yes, you had share ability earlier as well, but now we have separate button. On click it will show dropdown with&#xA;all available social networks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/&#34;&gt;webtor.io&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;sponsor it&lt;/a&gt; if you wish!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.3.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 15:24:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.3.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of new features:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dark/Light mode&lt;/strong&gt; - now &lt;strong&gt;webtor.io&lt;/strong&gt; will automatically switch theme according to your system preferences.&#xA;Also it is possible to switch between modes with &amp;ldquo;Dark/Light mode&amp;rdquo; button at the right top corner of the screen (near language selector).&#xA;This blog gains this feature too (but without switch button).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sponsor access&lt;/strong&gt; - if you &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;become a sponsor&lt;/a&gt; somehow then you can access additional features with special &lt;strong&gt;sponsor access&lt;/strong&gt;.&#xA;Just click &amp;ldquo;Already a Sponsor? Login here!&amp;rdquo; link near &amp;ldquo;Sponsor&amp;rdquo; button and you will be authorized through &lt;strong&gt;Patreon&lt;/strong&gt;.&#xA;If you have any active tiers then all connected offers will be activated. (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;Learn more about tiers&amp;hellip;&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open-sourcing&lt;/strong&gt; - here is one thing that people sometimes asking me. It is &amp;ldquo;How to run webtor at my own server?&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;I haven&amp;rsquo;t planned it before, but now I decided to start open-sourcing all parts of this project (backend, frontend and Google Chrome Extension).&#xA;This task is not simple and can take a lot of time and effort.&#xA;But something was already made right now. &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/webtor-io/&#34;&gt;Here it is!&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/&#34;&gt;webtor.io&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?u=24145874&#34;&gt;sponsor it&lt;/a&gt; if you wish!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 20:02:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.2.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of new features:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open magnet-urls&lt;/strong&gt; - now it is possible to open magnet-url with &amp;ldquo;Open torrent online&amp;rdquo; button.&#xA;There&amp;rsquo;s a special arrow near the &amp;ldquo;Open torrent online&amp;rdquo; button. After a click on it you will find a list of recent torrents and also field for pasting magnet-url.&#xA;After pasting of valid url there will open the a window with the torrent.&#xA;File list may not appear right away, it takes time to fetch torrent-file from the peers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real progress bar&lt;/strong&gt; - earlier progress bar shows only what portion of file was downloaded (downloaded bytes from total). But now it shows what specific pieces of file were downloaded (beginning, middle or end). It represents real status of the torrent pieces.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;External subtitles encoding detection&lt;/strong&gt; - earlier there was a problem with usage of SRT-subtitles with encoding that differs from UTF-8, part of the symbols (or whole of them) might be corrupted.&#xA;Now original subtitle encoding is detected automatically and subtitles are converted to WebVTT with UTF-8 encoding.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feedback form&lt;/strong&gt; - now you have an opportunity to write feedback about any issue occurred, also you can just suggest any new feature with our new &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/support&#34;&gt;feedback form&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for using &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io/en/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;webtor.io&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Webtor 1.1.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 23:27:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-features-in-webtor-1.1.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of new features:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In-place player&lt;/strong&gt; - from this moment all video and images are opening just below selected file. There is no need to scroll up to find the player anymore!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Copy stream url&lt;/strong&gt; - now you can copy currently playing video stream url and place it to VLC or any other player. Just go to player settings page and find &amp;ldquo;Copy stream url&amp;rdquo; button.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Current revision&lt;/strong&gt; - at the top left corner here is a small revision number with the link to release notes (page like this).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reduced script size&lt;/strong&gt; - there was a lot of work done to reduce size of all script bundles up to 3 times. Now &lt;strong&gt;Webtor&lt;/strong&gt; loads faster after updates.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s all folks!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New extension for Google Chrome Webtor.io 0.1.10</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-extension-for-google-chrome-webtor.io-0.1.10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:13:37 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-extension-for-google-chrome-webtor.io-0.1.10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This minor update solves annoying problem with automatic opening of downloaded torrent-files on several sites (&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-movies-online-from-yts.am/&#34;&gt;yts.am&lt;/a&gt; for example).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To make it working we need to check that &amp;ldquo;Allow Access to file URLs&amp;rdquo; option is enabled. Follow these steps:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We need to be sure that &lt;a href=&#34;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/webtorio-watch-torrents-o/ngkpdaefpmokglfnmienfiaioffjodam&#34;&gt;Webtor.io extension&lt;/a&gt; is already installed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Go to Google Chrome&amp;rsquo;s extensions page &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-extension-for-google-chrome-webtor.io-0.1.10/step1.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Find Webtor.io extension and click &amp;ldquo;Details&amp;rdquo; &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-extension-for-google-chrome-webtor.io-0.1.10/step2.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Option &amp;ldquo;Allow Access to file URLs&amp;rdquo; should be activated &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-extension-for-google-chrome-webtor.io-0.1.10/step3.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After accomplishing these steps you should not meet any problems with opening of downloaded torrent-files.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Webtor 1.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/introducing-webtor-1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:15:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/introducing-webtor-1.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of improvements were done this year that make it possible to tag current version as 1.0. Hurrah! &amp;#x1f389;&amp;#x1f389;&amp;#x1f389;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So here is a list of most major changes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Seeking&amp;rdquo; support for transcoded audio and video content&lt;/strong&gt; - now you can play mkv-movies from the middle (not only from the beginning as it was before).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Access to transcoding settings for video content&lt;/strong&gt; - now it is possible to choose specific audiotrack and subtitles.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Continue watching from&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; - player remembers last playback position and suggest to start from that position next time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open recent torrent&lt;/strong&gt; - you can just click small arrow near &amp;ldquo;Open torrent online&amp;rdquo; button and the list of recently watched torrents appears.&#xA;It also remembers last accessed folder as well.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Last watched content&lt;/strong&gt; - all watched content is marked with &amp;#x2714;&amp;#xfe0f; sign.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social sharing&lt;/strong&gt; - now you can share content link as you used to on the other sites. Just click on icon of your preferred social network and share content you are watching right now.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And also I&amp;rsquo;ve started this blog! That&amp;rsquo;s why you know right now about all improvements!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch movies online from nyaa.si</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-movies-online-from-nyaa.si/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:26:03 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-movies-online-from-nyaa.si/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nyaa.si is specialized in anime movie releases and also it has additional categories like books, audio, etc&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are few simple steps to start watch movie online without need of download:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Go to the torrent page.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click &amp;ldquo;Download Torrent&amp;rdquo; link. &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-movies-online-from-nyaa.si/step2.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You should see downloaded torrent file in your browser. &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-movies-online-from-nyaa.si/step3.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Go to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io&#34;&gt;webtor site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click &amp;ldquo;Open torrent online&amp;rdquo; button and choose your downloaded torrent file. &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../open-torrent.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;After that you will see content of the torrent file.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click on the movie file (it has .mp4 or .mkv extension) and wait for a little before playback begins. &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-movies-online-from-nyaa.si/step7.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PS: You can skip steps (3-5) if you install &lt;a href=&#34;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/webtorio-watch-torrents-o/ngkpdaefpmokglfnmienfiaioffjodam&#34;&gt;webtor chrome extension&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch movies online from yts.am</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-movies-online-from-yts.am/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 14:30:02 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-movies-online-from-yts.am/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yts.am (or yts.lt) is specialized in movie releases and has really good catalog to choose from.&#xA;Every single movie has trailer, poster and description. Also it is possible to choose&#xA;quality of the content (720p or 1080p, BluRay or Web).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are few simple steps to start watch movie online without need of download:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Go to the movie page.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click green download button under the main poster. &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-movies-online-from-yts.am/step2.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click download one more time in the opened popup window under desired quality. &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-movies-online-from-yts.am/step3.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You should see downloaded torrent file in your browser. &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-movies-online-from-yts.am/step4.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Go to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://webtor.io&#34;&gt;webtor site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click &amp;ldquo;Open torrent online&amp;rdquo; button and choose your downloaded torrent file. &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../open-torrent.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;After that you will see content of the torrent file.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click on the movie file (it has .mp4 extension) and wait for a little before playback begins. &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/watch-movies-online-from-yts.am/step7.png&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PS: You can skip steps (4-6) if you install &lt;a href=&#34;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/webtorio-watch-torrents-o/ngkpdaefpmokglfnmienfiaioffjodam&#34;&gt;webtor chrome extension&lt;/a&gt;.&#xA;&lt;del&gt;Unluckily this extension doesn&amp;rsquo;t handle torrent downloads from yts.am and you should click magnet-link instead.&#xA;And it will take some time (up to a minute or so) to gather torrent content from peers (be patient).&lt;/del&gt;&#xA;Please follow &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/new-extension-for-google-chrome-webtor.io-0.1.10/&#34;&gt;this guide&lt;/a&gt; to make extension fully compatible&#xA;with yts.am&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
