<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Torrent Basics on webtor.io</title>
    <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/series/torrent-basics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Torrent Basics on webtor.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 21:47:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.webtor.io/en/series/torrent-basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Do you really need a VPN for torrents?</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/vpn-for-torrents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 21:47:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/vpn-for-torrents/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For many people, torrents and VPNs are almost inseparable.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever searched for anything related to torrenting, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably seen the same advice repeated over and over: &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Always use a VPN.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But is that actually true in every case?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And more importantly — &lt;strong&gt;what exactly changes depending on how you download or stream torrents?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s break it down without myths or marketing promises.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-people-use-vpns-with-torrents&#34;&gt;Why people use VPNs with torrents&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main reason VPNs are commonly recommended for torrents comes from how &lt;strong&gt;traditional torrent clients&lt;/strong&gt; work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webtor.io vs WebTorrent vs μTorrent Web</title>
      <link>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/webtor.io-vs-webtorrent-vs-%CE%BCtorrent-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 18:09:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.webtor.io/en/post/webtor.io-vs-webtorrent-vs-%CE%BCtorrent-web/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello! This time I decided to write some comparison of my service and other similar ones. Perhaps many&#xA;moments will seem a little biased to you, but alas, I have been developing this service for a long time and I can be a little subject.&#xA;I can also write a little bit more detailed about my service because I know it a little better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The BitTorrent protocol has been around since 2001 and is used to transfer files, videos and music to this day,&#xA;despite various restrictions in a number of countries. During this time, a large number of BitTorrent clients appeared,&#xA;implementing this protocol, with the ability to download and streaming.&#xA;If earlier the BitTorrent client was associated only with Desktop applications, now many of them&#xA;stepped towards web applications and suddenly opened in a web browser. Let&amp;rsquo;s try to figure it out&#xA;in this variety of Web-Torrent clients. For comparison were selected:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
